

MATAGA RALPH

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

CONTACT INFO

+263 737 437 047

rternal@outlook.com

Kodingwithternal.com

www.facebook.com/ternal

@ralphternal

28 Box, Plumtree

SKILLS

JAVASCRIPT

PHOTOSHOP

JAVA	
C++	
RUBY	
NODE JS	
HTML/CSS	
PYTHON	
WORDPRESS	
REFERENCES	

MICHAEL CHITIGA

Product Manager
0782595821
chitigamicha@gmail.com

MOSH HAMEDANI

Senior Developer 077718921 codewithmosh.com

ENAIDARH MARTINEZ

Product Manager
0789123782
enaidarhmart@yahoo.com

I'm a passionate young software engineer with 5 years of experince in the field. I love and have been working as a Desktop and Games Application Developer.

I'm also Data Scientist, which is one of the most trending opportuniy and recent technology that utilizes Python programming.

EXPERIENCE

MICROSOFT

2016 - 2018

JUNIOR DEVELOPER

Once worked as an application back-end junior developer at MS Corporations.

GOOGLE INC

2018 - 2020

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

Respnso

GOOGLE INC

2019 - 2020

LEAD WEB DEVELOPER

I'm also a skilled personal when it comes to Front-End Web Developmet. Worked as the leader for a web based projec.

APPLE

2020 - Present

SENIOR DEVELOPER

Working as senior developer at Apple Inc. I'm responsible for producing and drawing conclusions about the design patterns and effective algorithms to help impliment with support from other team.

EDUCATION

ALHEIT HIGH

2005 - 2009

SECONDARY

I did my secondary education at Alheit High School in Gutu Masvingo. Results: 8As 2Bs Did wrote ten subjects and passed all of them.

ALHEIT HIGH

2010 - 2012

A - LEVELS

With passes in my A-Level with 13 points in MPC(Computers).

Maths: A Physics: C Computers: A

HARARE INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY UNIVERSITY

2013 - 2015

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

A First Class B.Tech Hnrs Degree holder in Software Engineering, certificate in Technopreneurship from Zimbabwean most accredited technoprenueral university.

AWARDS

MICROSOFT

June 2017

EXCELLENT WORK

I was once a Project Manager for the Windows (OS) Maintanance works. I did produced best plans, projects meeting deadlines and many more with other project team and stakeholders.

ALPHABET INC

Feb 2016

THE STAR EMPLOYEE

I was awarded the best prize for my outstanding performance, being an ethical person and a model in the organization.



Download CV